REDUX REDUX
Specials are up on the board, doll.
Let me get you a menu.
Hon?
Sorry.
Let me give you a little advice.
Pick somethin'
from the first page.
'Cause that fancy stuff
in the back?
They don't come out looking
like the pictures.
I... I don't want anything
from the kitchen.
I uh, I gotta get goin'.
Well, let me get you somethin'
for the road.
You look like you could use it.
Thanks, Deb.
♪ Build me up ♪
♪ Build me up again ♪
♪ Tear me down ♪
♪ Tear me down again ♪
♪ Build me up ♪
♪ Build me up again ♪
♪ Tear me down ♪
♪ Tear me down again ♪
♪ Ah ♪
Where's her body?
Who the fuck are you?
-Number 12.
-You wanna live?
Tell me anything about her.
What's her name?
What'd she look like?
Where is she?
Her name was Anna.
She lived her whole life
in 14 years.
For what?
To cross paths with you?
To get discarded in a ditch?
H... h... hold on.
-Where is she?
-Do you even remember?
Please.
Shit.
Need a little time to look over
this menu, hon?
Who's working in the kitchen?
-I don't know.
-Uh, Gustavo and Marvin.
You lookin' for somebody?
Deb! Can you get that?
Neville's not working?
There was a hair in my burger,
that's disgusting.
I want a refund...
She... she ate the whole thing.
Oh, I'm telling you she put it
in there on purpose
and I could get sick...
Cream and sugar?
Hold it.
Don't move.
Don't move!
Wait!
Hey, can I help you find
what you're looking for?
All good, thanks!
Uh, ma'am, I'm gonna need
to see your rental agreement.
Ma'am?
Ma'am, stop the car!
Ma'am, get out of the car, okay?
Stop!
-Move!
-Oh, oh shit!
"Police Radio warning".
In pursuit of suspect.
Fuck.
Fu...
Shit.
Hold it! Hold it!
Hold it!
Come out of there!
Open the door!
I said, open up!
Get the fuck out of there!
-Breach! Breach!
-Breach!
Yeah, uh, do you have
any adjoining rooms?
No.
Or... or two rooms next
to each other with a cot?
I can put you in like,
room 12 and 13.
-Hi, sorry.
-Hi, can I stay in that room?
Uh, I'm sorry, what?
Sorry, I... I know this is weird,
it's just um, the door
was already open, so...
My stuff is inside already.
Hey there.
-Hi.
-Oh, hi.
You don't have a lighter,
by any chance?
I... if you asked me
two weeks ago,
I would've, but I just quit.
I'm so sorry.
-Damn.
-You sure you quit?
Not just,
taking a little vacation?
Uh, I'm pretty sure.
I don't, I... I have uh,
nicotine gum.
Uh...
But,
It's a bit sweaty.
How can I resist?
Are you new here?
It's not that frightening
when you get down there.
Yeah, I've been uh, going
to a similar one.
Honestly, it just feels
like some nights of beer
might do me better.
-Yeah.
-I hear that.
What do you think?
-To uh, for a beer?
-To get a beer?
For the... for the,
like, the two of us?
Yeah.
Unless you gave that up, too.
Listen, I uh,
I can't go down there.
Let me buy you a beer.
Or a Seven and Seven.
Well, that's my drink.
My first meeting uh,
it's I think a month
after my wife passed away,
and I was uh, emoti... I was...
uh, it was rou... it was bad.
And I showed up late,
and apologized to everybody,
came in, sat down, and this guy
was telling a story
about uh, falling off the wagon
and crashing his car into
a turnpike in an interstate.
And the next woman started
talking about making meth
in this meth... I realized
I was in the wrong meeting.
Yeah.
And I'm watching everybody
tell their stories,
and at that point
I didn't realize
that you didn't have to share
when you came to the meeting,
so I was terrified
that I'm gonna get called out
for being a narc if I don't tell
an equally-horrifying story.
So I'm racking my...
and I've never seen hard drugs
in my life, but I'm thinking
about maybe my back stories
that I was doing meth
and hit rock bottom,
like dissolving a guy in a bath.
I was thinking
about Breaking Bad.
I was thinking about
every episode of break...
I was trying to remember.
But uh, when the time came,
I apologized,
and anyway,
that was my first session.
Well, I uh, I spent my first
session trying to...
Muster up the courage
to talk about my daughter,
and this 20-year-old kid,
I mean, this teenager is...
is an emotional wreck
in the corner,
just like loud, ugly crying,
so I... I stopped, you know,
to let him take the floor,
thinking he just got orphaned.
Sure.
But as it turns out, his
girlfriends just dumped him.
Like, come on, dude, you know,
keep it together.
You lost your daughter?
It was a long time ago.
Uh, excuse me can...
can we close out?
You wanna get out of here?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Is your place close by?
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Irene?
I don't know if you remember me.
I'm Mrs. Baker.
I had you for ninth grade
algebra.
Uh, I... I think you got me
mixed up with someone else.
Irene Kelly?
Mom, that's not her.
What?
-That's not her.
-She's gone, mom.
They found her after
her daughter died.
Oh my God, that's right.
I... I'm sorry.
She was an old student of mine.
You look just like her.
You know what, um,
I gotta get going.
Oh.
Hey.
Sorry, this is stupid.
-No, I'm sorry.
-Uh, that was uh, wild.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I don't know.
That... that woman just, she got
me mixed up with someone else
and it just kind of
wigged me out, I guess.
I... I just feel like I
shouldn't really be here.
Is this 'cause she knew
your name
and that was...
and then she said
that they found you
after your daughter die...
It's... I... can we acknowledge
that was just a bit...
I just... I'm playing catch up
here.
I'm glad you gave up smoking.
Think you finally turned
a corner.
You don't need me fucking
things up for you.
You look good, Jonathan.
Can I tell you something?
Yeah, sure.
We've met before.
When?
Last week.
And the week before that.
And then we uh,
we go to this bar
and then we fuck in your car.
Okay.
It's the closest thing I have
to a monogamous relationship.
Are you lacing these with PCP
or...
What are you talking about?
I've wanted to tell you
for a really long time.
We've met and fucked
hundreds of times
in different parallel universes.
I've been traveling
through them.
I uh,
I stayed in one universe
with you for two months.
What is this?
When did you do this?
Don't be scared.
I... I've been traveling
through them looking
for my daughter.
Looking for a world where she
wasn't kidnapped and murdered.
But every universe is just like
the one before it.
They're all the same.
The changes are so small,
you can barely notice them.
She's been dead in all of them.
So I just keep killing
the bastard who did this to her,
over and over, and over again.
I can't stop.
I can't quit.
He's taken everything from me.
I don't even know
what I am anymore.
So what can I get you, hon?
Is Neville working tonight?
He called out sick.
He a friend of yours?
No.
Oh, shit!
Who the fuck are you?
-It's okay, it's okay.
-I'm not gonna hurt you.
Get the fuck away from me!
Listen, I can help you.
Back up!
Oh, God!
Shit.
I'm on your side.
Let's get you out of here.
Come on.
Listen, if he gets a jump on us,
stick him in the belly and run.
Oh shit.
It's okay.
Is he here?
He's gone.
You're gonna be okay.
You don't need to worry
about him.
-I'll take care of it...
-He got away.
I'll find him.
There's a police station
a few blocks from...
No, no way.
-Where do you live?
-I'll bring you home.
Look, I gotta bring
you somewhere.
I'm so hungry.
I'll take you wherever you want.
You know, someone's worried
sick about you.
I doubt it.
Where do you live?
A group home on Fletcher.
Bunch of kids
with behavioral problems.
That dude snatched me
the same day I snuck out,
what are the fucking odds?
You're a runaway.
You know, he picked me up like
five blocks from my place.
Said he was looking for his dog.
And I believed him.
Such a fucking idiot.
No, you're not.
I mean, it's not like
he was in a rapist van
or something.
It was broad daylight.
He was wearing a tie
for fuck's sake.
He was?
I know.
What a fucking psycho.
I mean, who swings by
the dry cleaners
before kidnapping kids?
So, how'd you know
I was in there?
I didn't.
What were you doing there?
Doesn't matter.
You were gonna kill him.
That was the idea.
You think the cops will get him?
I will.
How?
There's a place in Echo Canyon.
It's condemned,
but he squats there sometimes
when he wants to lay low.
How long have you been trying
to kill this guy?
Long time.
Need any help?
We should get you home.
Fuck that place.
Seriously, just 'cause I try
to run a few times,
they sticking me
with all the crazies.
How far is Echo Canyon?
You don't wanna go there.
Trust me, lady, I'd like to see
what this guy has coming to him.
I'll never sleep again.
You gotta understand that.
I mean, knowing he could still
be out there.
I just need to know he's dead.
I'll wait in the fucking car
if I have to.
I just need to know.
Look, I'm sorry.
I really am,
but it's not gonna happen.
You're going home.
You're gonna tell the police
what happened
and everyone's gonna find out
who he really is.
Thanks for the food.
I should get home.
Can I uh, borrow some money?
-Uh, yeah.
-I've got some cash in my pack.
Mind if I take your singles?
Vending machine at the police
station won't take fives.
Been there a few times?
You know, you want anything
more than a granola bar,
those pricks charge you for it.
Take whatever you need.
Thanks.
Well, thanks again.
You getting in?
Police station's
just a block up.
Yeah, I'll drive you closer.
Nah, I should walk.
I mean, probably better
if I don't show up with Mad Max.
Hey, be safe.
Yeah.
Thanks, I mean it.
Shit.
Motherfucker.
"Background mumbling audio."
Another 50 rounds of Winchester
thirty-eights.
Hi.
Cute kid.
Oh, thanks.
Uh, do you think maybe you
could buy me something?
-Oh, no, sorry.
-I don't have any cash.
No, I... I have money.
No, look, I can't buy you beer.
No, no, no.
I... I don't want beer.
I just uh, need somethin' else.
What?
Bullets?
-Sorry, never mind.
-I... I'm kidding.
I'm just fucking around.
That's...
Hey, sorry, uh, do you think
you could help me with this?
It's a little too high up
for me.
Yeah, of course.
This is what you want?
Uh, yep.
So you want a toilet?
Yeah.
Alright.
-Hey!
Security!
Shoplifter!
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, calm down, calm down.
You need a ride?
Keep rolling, pervert.
Whoa, no.
I... just trying to help.
I'm waiting for a woman to
stop. Thanks.
How old are you?
Dude, move on.
You shouldn't be hitching
on the side of a highway,
alright? It's dangerous.
Thanks, dad.
I... I just don't wanna see
you on the news, okay?
Look, if you're gonna hitch,
there's a rest stop
a couple miles ahead.
I'm not getting in your car.
Oh, shit.
Where you headed?
Echo Canyon.
Hop aboard.
You a runaway?
I'm 18.
That right?
Yeah.
You look like you're still
in diapers.
You look old enough
to need 'em again.
Damn, girl.
I just picked your ass up from
the side of the road.
Sorry.
Thank you for picking me up.
I had to fend off about half
a dozen creeps looking
for more than a passenger.
I guess I'm a little on edge.
-It's okay.
-I get it.
Hitchhiking at your age, you
gotta have a little bark in you.
You're not uh, looking for more
than a passenger, right?
-You can trust me.
-I've been in your shoes before.
Canyon's about two hours north.
You need to stop
for a piss break?
You can just let me know.
Don't worry.
I'm house trained.
Whoa, whoa.
What?
Where are you taking me?
You're a little jumpy,
aren't you?
I'm not fucking around.
-It's okay, honey.
-It's a check stop.
We're getting lunch.
You're okay.
So, what brings
you to Echo Canyon?
Unfinished business.
Well, that's cryptic as shit.
You spend um, some vacation time
there or something?
No.
See it on a postcard?
Nope.
Some boyfriend you met online?
Definitely not.
Well, that's what got me,
young love.
-I met a girl.
-She was older.
Obviously, things were
different back then.
Parents were assholes about it?
Oh, no, no.
I was never gonna tell them
about that.
I wasn't gonna give them
a chance to give me
the come-to-Jesus talk.
So I just took off.
I spent a whole weekend
with this girl in Long Beach.
My parents thought
that I was, you know,
at a sleepover somewhere.
Back then,
we didn't have cell phones,
so they had to call around,
and it took them a day
and a half before
they called the police.
And when they finally did,
I was home an hour later.
I ran away for two days.
Didn't like what I saw.
Well, doesn't really sound like
you gave it a fair shake.
I mean, everything's scary
two days in.
Well, that's a good point, yeah.
Wise words.
Uh, trouble was that I had been
dreaming about taking off
for the whole summer
and when I finally did,
I find out the girl
that I had been seeing,
had been carrying on
with other people.
I wasn't the only one.
And um, reality set in,
and then I had to go back,
and tell my parents.
They pissed?
I was pissed.
I was angry.
I was confused.
And I... I was ready
to take it on the chin,
but you know what happened?
They weren't mad at all.
-I don't know.
-They felt really sorry for me.
I see.
They said growing up is hard,
but it gets easier.
I get it.
Yeah.
Mm.
Thanks for the sage wisdom.
No, listen, all I am saying
is that life gets hard,
and you don't have
to do it alone.
Yeah, yeah.
Listen, lady, I'm not running
from my problems.
I'm heading straight for 'em.
Well, that's not
what I'm saying.
Everything okay?
-Uh, yeah.
-Just gotta run to the bathroom.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just gotta drain the dragon.
-Drain the dragon?
-What?
You have something
that belongs to me.
Get off me.
Where is it?
I hocked it for bus money
to the canyon.
You didn't bring it
to a crowded restaurant.
Don't make me fire
a warning shot.
It's empty.
Oh, you sure about that?
Christ, what is wrong with you?
Take your hands off her.
Uh, no, you don't understand.
Yeah?
Maybe you wanna explain it
to the police.
Uh, she's my aunt.
Yeah.
Tracked me down, figured out
I was going to the canyon,
so jig is up.
You sure everything's okay?
Yeah.
We should probably hit the
road, right.
I can call the police.
That's not necessary.
I don't like the way you were
getting physical with her.
Well, she's not the one
picking up minors
from the highway rest stop.
Wow.
You mean the breakdown lane, honey.
You're lucky
you're not roadkill.
You were hitchhiking?
Almost got herself killed.
What do you expect?
It's not exactly like
I have bus fare money.
Oh, uh, Darla bought me
some pancakes,
so you might wanna slip her
somethin' for the trouble.
I'll be in the car.
No.
-Come on.
-We're really doing this again.
You need to give me the gun
and you need to go home.
I'm a hundred miles away.
It's not my problem.
Alright.
Fine, I'll go back in there
and ask toothless Joe
to give me a ride back
in his semi.
I'm sure I won't end up
in a ditch somewhere.
You want the gun,
I come with it.
You want me to go back in there
and have Darla call the cops,
that's fine by me.
Good luck explaining that one.
You're gonna do
everything I tell you
for the next 24 hours,
you got it?
You're gonna be quiet.
You're gonna wait in the hotel
when I tell you to
and tomorrow I'm dropping you
off at the police station
and you're going home.
Are we clear?
Cool.
Yeah, great, okay.
Mmhmm.
See, that's all I'm asking.
Be outta your hair in no time.
So, when are we doin'
this thing?
We'll get the jump on him
right before dawn.
We're not going now?
He's paranoid at night,
lets his guard down
in the morning.
Uh, not to tell you how to do
your job or anything,
but it kinda feels like he got
the jump on you last time.
You know what?
You're the boss,
morning is great.
There's a motel up the road,
you'll stay there.
Okay.
And no sneaking over
after I leave
or stowing away in my truck
or any other kind of bullshit
like that, okay?
-Yeah.
-Mmhmm.
Guy's got razor wire all over
his property.
If you don't know
where you're going,
you'll get caught up in it,
I promise.
Where are we going?
Dinner.
Here?
Diner's closed.
Convenience store has hot dogs
and those taquito things.
Gross.
The fuck is that?
It's nothing.
-Didn't look like nothin'.
-Looked like a fucking bomb.
It's not a bomb.
Look, if you're gonna nuke
the whole lake,
I just kinda feel like you
should disclose that to me.
-It's not a bomb.
-Just stay away from it.
Grab somethin' to eat,
train's leaving in five minutes.
Oh, hi.
Kitchen's closed.
Uh, chef got sick, so probably
dodging a bullet there.
Uh, but let me know
if you need anything.
Can I get 40 on three?
Yeah.
Regular?
Supreme?
Uh, regular will do it, thanks.
No one ever takes the supreme.
-Hey.
-What do you think you're doin'?
Oh, uh, nothing, sorry.
Oh, no, no, no, not so fast.
Uh.
Care to explain yourself?
What's going on?
Yeah, it's yours.
-What are you doin'?
-I...
Did you take anything else?
No, sorry.
She's a bit of a klepto,
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're not getting off
that easy.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Hey, uh, that is not necessary.
Afraid it is?
Hey, yeah, this is Gus
over at Rest Stop 38.
Got another one of those kids
tryna steal a bottle of wine.
She looks like she's 12.
I'm 15, asshole.
Mia.
And she's cursing now.
I know.
Okay, thank you.
On their way.
Dude, I said I'm sorry.
She'll pay for it, okay?
I'm not letting her
buy you booze.
What do you think this is?
What the fuck is your problem?
Easy.
Whoa!
Stand There,
Oh shit!
No!
Give me the slugs.
The bullets!
Count of three.
Go out that door.
Run for the truck.
Hide in the back.
Got it?
Mia.
Okay.
1, 2, 3.
Fuck.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-Hold up!
Hands in the air!
-Hands in the air!
-Fuck.
No, no, no, no!
Don't shoot!
Who else is in there?
Some fucking crazy lady.
Sir, stay where you are!
Oh, shit!
Freeze!
Back up, we need backup.
Get in.
Mia, get in the machine.
Let's go.
This is gonna hurt.
-What the fuck?
What the fuck?
-It's okay.
It's okay.
No, don't!
Shut it!
Are you fucking crazy?
What the?
It's okay.
What the fuck just happened?
I can explain.
But first, we gotta get
this thing out of here, okay?
Oh, hey.
How are you?
Got a little blood on you
there, hon?
Do you want a... a Band-Aid?
On the house, of course.
Yeah, thanks.
How much for
the pick-up outside,
the for sale sign?
Askin' price is 1,200.
You wanna take it
for a test drive?
Does it run?
You bet, yeah.
I'll take it.
How much for a bottle of wine?
Hey, when You take this truck
off my hands,
you can have any bottle
you want.
-What the fuck is that thing?
-A time machine?
-No.
-It's not a time machine.
Are you tryna tell me I just
dreamt all that shit up?
That you didn't just go all
Grand Theft Auto in there?
You didn't dream it.
This is gonna be hard
to understand.
We live in a multiverse.
What?
It's a series of...
I know what a multiverse is.
You do?
-I go to school.
-You know that, right?
They teach that
in high school physics?
Creative writing.
Right.
It's not like sliding doors,
if that's what you are thinking.
What the fuck is sliding doors?
It's just more complicated.
So that's how a guy goes from
dead one moment to living
in the next?
We didn't bring him back to
life.
He was just never shot
in this universe.
So where I'm from,
that poor guy's either
in a hospital bed or a morgue.
Unfortunately, yeah.
So if he's dead in that universe
and living in this one,
then so is Neville.
Not for long.
Shit! Irene! Irene!
Irene,
the fucking car's on fire!
Fuck.
What happened?
What the hell is that?
A flux capacitor?
It's a battery.
What does that mean?
It means we're a little fucked.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, thanks.
You can watch TV if you want.
Run a movie.
Whatever.
How long have you
been doin' this?
-I don't know.
-Long time.
Years?
-I gotta get some stuff done.
-Go ahead.
Watch TV or something.
How many times
have you killed him?
A lot.
Dozens?
Cold.
Hundreds?
Still cold.
Well, shit.
More times
than I can keep track.
Hey.
Go easy on that.
After the day I've had?
There's something else.
You can't go home
to your universe.
At least not for a while.
Why not?
After what happened
at the gas station,
our faces, mine in particular,
will be all over the news,
the papers, everywhere.
A machine can get me out
of a universe,
but not if I'm locked up.
For how long?
I don't know.
A few weeks.
Gotta play it smart.
But we'll get you home soon.
I promise.
Okay, maybe this was a bad idea.
How many times do we get
to kill him?
What?
Well, I mean, if we can't go
back for a few weeks,
do we just break into his house
and uh...
Every day, or we take
weekends off?
I kill him.
Sure, how often?
Thursdays.
Why Thursdays?
He gets paid on Thursday.
Oh.
Jesus.
Yeah, I'm not proud of it,
but somebody's gotta pay
the bills.
And Neville's funding his own
assassination squad.
-No, not squad.
-Singular.
Just me.
Lady, you dragged me through
the looking glass.
There's no going back now.
Okay.
Wha...
Hey, I wasn't finished
with that.
Yes, you are.
Look, I get you think
you want vengeance.
I'm telling you, you don't.
Not bringing a child with me
to go kill someone.
It's just not happening.
I'm not a kid.
I've been in the system
since I was 4 years old.
Six foster homes.
I've been knocked down, beat up,
and pushed around more times
than I can count.
And when you complain,
they just ship you off
to a place that's worse
than the last.
First time I lied about a
bruise was in the third grade.
I knew if I said something,
they'd just ship me off,
and I'd never see my best friend
in the foster home again.
Eventually, they shuffled us
around anyway
and I haven't seen her in years.
You think this guy is bad?
He's just the latest
in the long line
of assholes and dirt bags
that I've had to deal with.
I've been knocked around
my whole life.
For once,
I'd just like to hit back.
Nobody can kill him until
we have an escape plan.
And we're not going anywhere
until we get a new fuel core.
Well, where the fuck
do we get one of those?
Better hope some smugglers
are passing through.
Hey, you get The Chronicle?
Not until 6:00 a.m.
What about today's?
Dumpster.
Who's Jack Klaxon?
Ten letters.
He's not a person.
He's a phone number.
Write what I tell you.
3, 4, 4.
7, 0, 0.
1, 1, 8.
1, 9, 6.
This is some Bourne Identity
shit right here.
What are those?
Coordinates?
Yep.
Fuck yeah.
Shit.
We missed them.
What are we even looking for?
-It's always different.
-Usually hiding in plain sight.
Flea markets.
Way stations.
Abandoned houses.
Never really know
what you'll get.
So, what do these guys
smuggle anyway?
Drugs and shit?
Easier ways to get drugs.
Then what?
People.
Most people who wanna get out
of their universe
can't get their hands
on a machine like mine.
They come to guys like this.
So, they're like
the underground railroad?
If you're lucky.
Well, what if you're unlucky?
Can I help you?
-Uh, yeah.
-Saw your ad in the classifieds.
-You got a funny accent.
-We from the same place?
I'm from 0-0.
Both of you?
Just me.
Looking to hitch a ride?
-Just looking for a part.
-Burned down my fuel core.
Hello?
Stop.
Step into my office.
Uh, nope.
My associate will see
what we can do for you.
Great.
The girl can hang back
here with me.
No, she's staying with me.
She's not from where we're from.
Am I right?
She's staying with me.
No worries.
Head on in.
My associate's on the way.
I can't see shit.
Takes a minute for the eyes
to adjust.
There's a couple seats
over there.
Just be a couple of minutes.
Can I get you ladies a Pepsi
or somethin'?
We're good.
Okay.
See you in a few.
-Wow.
-This is sketchy as fuck.
-It's okay.
-Just stay close.
He's here.
Listen, if anything goes
sideways, just get behind me.
-Hey.
-Sorry to uh, keep you waiting.
I'm Billie.
And you are?
Irene.
-You're not from around here.
-No.
-Great.
-Neither am I.
Uh, sorry if Travis like,
wigged you out a little bit.
He's uh, you know, gross.
But it's hard to find good help
in this line of work.
Uh, you ladies are lookin'
for a ride.
We've got a shipment going out
next Wednesday, if that works.
-We're good.
-Just need to fix up mine.
Fuel core went out.
-Oh, you've got your own.
-I love that.
Two independent gals just out
on the town.
Uh, what model
are you working with?
-The 375.
-Huh.
Those are usually pretty
sturdy, right?
-Yeah.
-I got a lot of miles on mine.
Well, yeah.
You're uh, pretty far out
from 0-0.
Unfortunately, we're not really
in the parts business.
You know, we're more like,
I don't know, tour guides.
It's not first class,
but we got an Epsilon 2 hundo.
You ever been
in an Epsilon series?
Uh...
They're built for like,
bigger payloads.
You know, cars,
equipment, whatever.
It's kind of a... a bumpy ride,
but it's not like the 375
is exactly a Lexus.
Right?
Uh, how about this?
You guys just leave your 375
with us,
and we'll give you as many
rides as you want.
Sound good?
I just need the part.
You sure?
I mean, it's not gonna be cheap.
You know,
I've seen those fuel cores last
like a thousand rides.
You guys skip many universes
on your way here?
Seen 'em all.
Goddamn.
You sure you can uh,
afford a new core?
You have one?
-Yeah.
-For sure.
It's uh, a bit pricey if you're
looking to pay cash or check,
but uh,
if it's a uh,
trade that you're looking for?
We're going.
Whoa, whoa, hold on.
Look, sorry, look, I...
I got the wrong impression.
Okay?
And chill out, no worries.
We're leaving.
-Look, okay, hold on.
-Travis!
Uh, bit of a faux pas
on my part,
but it's all good.
We're gonna chill out
and work something out.
-Let's go.
-10,000.
10,000 bucks and it's yours.
They go for 500 back home.
Does it look like
you're at home?
How much have you got?
2,200.
2,200 That's giving it away.
Hold on, Travis.
Whoa, Billie, we're not gonna
give it away.
Let's see the cash, and I'll see
if I have any refurbished ones
in my car.
How's that?
Fine.
-Great.
-Awesome.
Sit tight.
What a psycho fucking bitch.
We should get out of here.
It's alright, I've got my .38
in my waistband.
They try anything,
they'll get one in the forehead.
Yeah, you got your .38.
I got nothing but my dick
in my hands.
They get the jump on you,
I'm heading straight
for the Neverland Ranch.
Stop.
That all the cash you got left?
We'll get more on Thursday.
Not much of a negotiation
on my...
Hey!
Hey, come on!
Shit.
What the fuck is going on?
Fuck, we're in the machine.
Come on! Come on!
Hey, get us out of here!
-They are shipping us out.
-Hey!
Hey, Irene, get us out!
You want me to go?
No, no. Get down, get down!
Get in the truck!
Don't move, you little shit.
You know, we've got ways
to break little girls like you.
Hey, shut her the fuck up!
Fuck!
Don't!
Just leave her, let's go.
You're hardcore, Irene.
I mean it.
I shouldn't have brought
you there.
If you didn't bring me,
you'd be totally fucked.
No shit.
Good thing I got my hands
on a knife, huh?
Or else they'd be dumping
your body halfway
through the multiverse
right now.
You did good.
But you know, if she had a gun
and I got my hands on that,
I probably would have blown
my foot off.
Because I have no idea
how to shoot one.
I need to know
how to protect myself.
All right squeeze, don't pull.
And aim up the side on the back
with the one on the front.
Uh-huh.
And close one eye
if you have to.
All right, good.
It's getting better.
I'm a fucking natural!
All right, now this time
I want you to aim
and I want you to hold your
breath while you squeeze, okay?
Stay steady.
Okay.
Boom, bitch!
Yeah, well,
it took you five tries.
Only have to hit him once.
What is this place?
Used to be home.
Well, who lives here now?
Usually no one.
Sometimes basement window's
broken.
Teens leave empty beer bottles.
But more often than not,
people leave it alone.
-So, what happened to you?
-I mean, like parallel you.
She left.
Too painful to keep living here.
Well, we don't have to
stay here.
Those guys took the last
of our cash.
We'll squat here till Thursday.
-No, we don't have to do that.
-Listen, I'm easy.
We can camp out in the car.
I've had worse accommodations.
It's okay.
Warm shower,
roof over our heads.
I come here more often
than you think.
They uh, left a washer machine
in the back.
I'm gonna do a load
before I start working
on the fuel core.
Nice place.
It was, yeah.
Hot water's usually still on.
You can take a shower
if you want.
I've got some clean clothes
in my pack you can borrow.
Thanks.
Make yourself at home.
Oh, shit.
Hey.
I'd rather you didn't hang out
in here.
I'm really sorry.
What's in your hand?
Nothing.
Mia.
Are you dead?
I don't know how it happened
exactly.
Got some guesses, but...
They don't really uh, mention
how someone kills themselves
in their obituary.
Jesus.
Not like I can call someone
and ask.
So are you dead
in every other universe?
Looks like it, yeah.
What makes you different?
I don't know.
I had the machine.
My universe is the only one
I've seen that's discovered
multiverse travel.
And it gave me purpose.
When you lose a child,
people say you go numb.
But you don't go numb.
They put that word
in your mouth.
You go paralyzed.
Everything shuts down
except for your brain.
Keeps going in these mad spirals
that won't stop just racing.
Redlining.
Even when you sleep.
And just when you think
your brain is running so fast.
It just has to give out.
It doesn't quit.
It just keeps going, and going,
and going.
You wanna shut it down.
Reset it.
Just for a minute.
But when sleep, and booze,
and painkillers
won't quiet your brain
for even a minute,
you stop caring if it's a
minute or forever.
It just needs to shut down.
If I didn't have the machine,
if I couldn't go
looking for her,
what else could I do?
It's kept you alive.
It took everything from me.
I'm alive.
But I lost whatever humanity
I had left.
I'm not me anymore.
I don't even know what I am.
You don't have to make
the same mistake.
He doesn't deserve to live
in any universe.
Not after what he did to me.
What he did to Anna.
You don't want this.
Of course, I do.
-I can't stop.
-It's never over.
It's just this reoccurring
nightmare.
I know you think you want this,
but I'm telling you, you don't.
You won't...
You won't be you anymore.
You won't recognize
who you've become.
The other versions
of me had it better.
If it's between you or a version
of you that's hanging from
a ceiling fan,
I hate to break it to you,
but this doesn't seem so bad.
Maybe you hate yourself
a little bit, and that sucks,
but.
I'm sure as fuck glad
I ran into you.
If you never went looking,
I wouldn't be sitting here.
When we first came
to this universe,
I had this overwhelming feeling
like I wasn't supposed
to be here.
Like we weren't even supposed
to know each other.
But the more time
we spend together...
I feel like.
I don't know.
Like maybe
we were always
supposed to find each other.
Me too.
It's okay, it's okay.
Go back to sleep.
You're okay.
You're safe.
Where are we going?
You'll see.
I thought you hated fast food.
There's something
I gotta tell you.
The machine's fixed.
Okay.
We're going home.
What?
How'd you like to live with me?
Clean slate.
Start over.
Dude, what are you
talking about?
The machine's working.
We can walk right out
of this restaurant and go home.
We don't need to do this.
We'll walk away.
Live a normal life.
Fuck that.
We are doing this.
Irene, what the fuck
are you talking about?
We had a deal.
I went to his house last night.
It's over.
You already did it.
-You killed him?
-No.
Well, that's fucking bullshit.
Stop.
I'm going over there.
-No, you can't.
-You can't go back there.
You can't.
You can't see
what he did to you.
I'm dead?
He killed me?
Tell me.
Irene!
It's over.
Okay?
The only way to end it
is to just stop.
No! It's not...
It's not fucking over.
Not now.
He killed me.
I'm not gonna just let him
get away with that.
Are you fucking kidding me?
There's a version of me
that just had God knows
what happened to her.
My body's been left to rot
in his house
and you want to give him
a fucking pass?
No fucking way.
-He's gonna see me.
-See my fucking ghost.
I deserve that.
She deserves that.
It's done.
You're alive
and that's all that matters.
I can't risk him
doing that to you.
I'm not your daughter.
I'm not Anna.
-Don't push me.
-I'll go fucking nuclear.
We are doing this.
You're coming with me.
It's over.
She kidnapped me.
She fucking took me.
Hello?
She fucking took me!
Why the fuck
is nobody listening?
Hello?
What the fuck is wrong
with you people?
She fucking took me!
-What is this?
-She kidnapped me!
-Rick.
-Jesus, man.
-Okay, okay.
-Get off me!
-It's just a mis...
-Hey, hey, hey! Back up!
Back up!
Mia.
Liz, call the police.
Stop! Stop!
Yeah, this is FatBurger
and we need a police officer.
Shit.
Hey.
Hey, hey, whoa, hey.
-Hi.
Can I uh, can I bum a smoke?
-Uh, no.
-Yeah, I don't have any.
-Oh shit.
-Right, you... you quit.
-Sorry?
-Um.
Can I buy you a drink?
Seven and Seven?
Do you know me?
Do we know each other?
No. Um, uh, yes.
Yeah, we've met before.
Um, friend of a friend.
Okay.
How about it?
You wanna...
you wanna get out of here?
Are you here for grief support?
Um, sometimes I... I feel like
a beer might do me better.
Oh, okay.
Listen, um, I... I... I really
need someone to talk to.
I'm in a bad place and...
and if I don't talk to someone.
I... I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna fall back
into the same shit.
Can... can we hang out?
Fuck.
I'm fucking this up.
-No, it's okay.
-It's okay.
Uh, do you wanna come inside?
Do you wanna come to a meeting?
Forget it.
Sorry.
-Shit.
-Hey!
Hey!
Hey! What'd you take?
Hey! Hey, stop!
You okay, doll?
Yeah.
You sure?
Actually, I'm having a pretty
rough day.
Looks like maybe
you've had a few of those.
Wanna talk about it?
Do you have kids?
Yeah, they're grown now.
One of mine left today.
And I don't think
she's coming back.
She'll be back.
She's making the same mistakes
I did
and... and I... I'm just...
I'm just trying to, um...
-Let's get you something to eat.
-Hot meal?
Comfort food goes a long way.
It's just something kids do.
You know, she'll be back.
Come on, what do you say?
I know it doesn't look like it,
but we have got a hell of a
chef back in the kitchen.
Neville?
Who?
Neville.
You know him?
He haven't worked here
in like 15 years, hon?
What?
He's serving
three life sentences.
He's in prison?
How do you know him?
Did he do something to you?
Uh, 15... 15 years?
Are you all right?
Um, I... I've gotta go.
Oh, shit!
Mom, I thought you
were someone else.
What are you doing out here?
I missed you so much.
What happened to you?
It's okay.
I'm okay.
Don't be scared.
You're freaking me out, mom.
I'm not your mom.
What?
Be safe.
Don't talk to strangers.
Goodbye.
Shit.
I'm her fucking ghost!
You fucking bitch!
She had a sister?
She had a sister.
Shit.
Get me the fuck out of here!
Help!
Help me!
Your sister was rabid, too.
You got me good
with that revolver.
You and your sister
are a lot alike.
I still have no feeling
in my little finger.
She almost bit it clean off.
She's not my sister!
Ow, ow, fuck!
She's me!
You kill me now!
I'll haunt you the rest
of your fucking life!
Maybe I'll let you live
in there a little bit.
I put your sister down quick.
She bit me and I put her down
like a dog.
I'm thinking that's a bad idea.
Killing them quick is bad luck.
Yeah.
I'm gonna let you live
in there a little bit.
Hey, I'm gonna let you die slow.
Get me the fuck out of here!
Irene, help!
Somebody!
I'll tell you what.
You ask me real nice and sweet,
I'll put you down
quick and painless.
Did you like that?
Fuck you!
All right then.
-Mia!
-Irene!
You stay back!
You shoot again, she's dead!
Mia, are you okay?
Get me the fuck out of here!
You stand down!
Get away from her!
You come and get her!
Irene!
No!
Help!
Irene!
You shouldn't have come
out here.
-No!
Don't!
Shut up.
Stop.
Do I know you from somewhere?
You look familiar to me.
The news.
Right?
One of the mothers.
Is that it?
I remember now.
Your daughter had your eyes.
Go ahead.
You cannot go now.
Daughter's down there
waiting for you.
Are you okay?
Okay.
You came back.
I don't wanna do that again.
You'll never have to.